I'm so sorry. Can you help me? My tire.
Sorry I have an appointment. I don't let it be late.
Well, would you rather be late? Or dead.
You don't want to do this.
Step out of the car.
Woo! Let's go first! Come on, man!
Yeah!
Think it easy. The car's brand new.
No problem, buddy. I've got this.
Baby, that's right.
Baby, baby, I can show you.
Your parents know the kind of company you're keeping.
Shut up.
Shut up! It was my plan.
The shame, working, man! It's coded.
What's the code, man?
I'm afraid I can't get it down.
Well, I'm afraid we'll have to beat it out.
Let's go get out of this car.
Get out of the car, baby. Come on, man.
Baby, what you got to be fair?
What you got to be fair?
Keep doing it. Come on, baby.
Hold on.
This came out of the dry, man.
Ah!
Hands up!
Stop moving, I will shoot you.
What do you have home, what to do?
Why don't you go and do it?
Okay. I'm sorry.
Light.
Ah!
Hey, hey!
The game, the game, the game, the game!
What's the first rule one entering a man's car?
Respect the man's car, and then respects you.
Rule number two.
Greet the man.
Good afternoon, Frank.
Good afternoon, Jack.
Can we play the game now?
So you think your brain will be too tired after a whole day of school?
You're just afraid I'm gonna win.
I'm afraid you're gonna be too one out to do your homework.
It's Friday, I don't have any homework.
In that case, the game.
Yes!
But first, it's the third rule of the car.
Good.
Five points.
A white, a round, but I'm not always around.
A tennis ball.
A tennis ball's a yellow.
Four points.
Sometimes I'm habs, sometimes I'm whole, sometimes I'm slice of me as all you know.
A little for bread?
No.
Three points.
Sometimes I'm light, sometimes I'm dark, sometimes I'm both.
I know a light bulb.
No.
A pizza.
Audrey, stop walking away from me.
Listen, I've got to finish this conversation.
I've got about two minutes.
Where's he going?
He doesn't.
Okay, look at me.
Last clip for all the points.
Everyone wants to welcome me.
Not only happy if you ever have.
Take your time.
Hey, bud.
Hey, mom, it's the game.
I'm trying today.
Sorry.
Hey, Frank, how are you today?
Well, Mrs. Billings.
Frank, can I take a look with mom?
I don't know.
It's not in the rules.
Come on.
What's the point in having rules if you can't bend them?
Okay.
Just this once.
Yeah!
All right.
Do you need some goods?
It's round, but not always around.
It's like a ball.
It's like sometimes a duck, sometimes a both, sometimes.
Everyone wants to walk on it.
Only a happy few ever have.
That is a hard one.
Tell me about it.
The ball!
Correct.
Good job.
All right, come on.
See you Monday.
Hi, Frank. Thanks.
Keep your snacks in the kitchen.
Bye, mom.
Bye, honey.
He's really taken to you in the month you've been with us.
Likewise.
It's too bad you can't stay on after Tony gets back.
He's just a favor.
I don't usually do this sort of a job.
I thought you were a professional driver.
A different kind of driving.
Well, we're all going to miss you when you're gone.
And...
Thank you for what you did.
For what?
For turning the car around so the jack wouldn't have to see us fighting.
You really know kids don't you?
I know fighting.
He hasn't seen jack in months.
And then when he gets back here, all I can hear is what I'm doing wrong.
Think that you're going to be a good guy.
I'm going to be a good guy.
But that's what I'm doing wrong.
Think that after being separated for a year that he would...
I'm sorry.
You don't have to hear this.
It's okay.
What a swap I think you've done a great job with Jack.
Thank you.
Any time it can be of help is anything you need.
It's really sweet of you, Frank.
You might have to take you up on it.
Oh, uh, I almost forgot.
I'm supposed to take Jack to the doctor tomorrow morning
for his annual checkup, but I'm organizing a surprise party
for him, even though his birthday's not until next week.
What are we doing?
I'm going to go for a few days.
Oh, while I decorate, and his friends arrive,
I was thinking if you wouldn't mind.
I'll tell you, Kim.
I feel kind of funny cutting into your weekend.
Just picking up a friend at the airport later on in the day.
Hmm.
That's nice.
What is?
The guy's on security, say, a bit of a loner.
So it's just nice to hear you have a friend.
He's not really a friend.
He's French.
Look how you back.
Audrey, I'd like to finish our conversation.
Well, if anything comes up between now and then you have myself.
Nothing will come up with this, his feelings.
Audrey.
Yeah, hello.
I'm coming for tomorrow.
My name.
Yeah.
The murder you gave, will we change?
You drive me to take it in not the mother.
Even better.
Where am I?
Who shot?
Thank you.
Is this table?
Yes, it's still.
The antidote?
See you tomorrow, John.
And in other news, the drug-eaten force administers of six Latin American countries
arrived in Miami today for a summit meeting
with Jefferson building.
Come on, Frank.
1156 Palmello, way for an express delivery.
That's what you told me 45 minutes ago.
Well, I don't need anything else.
Just give me the pizza.
I'm not paying for that.
Hi.
So, Mr. Martin, that's one medium-time, no mozzarella, extra olives, and extra anchovies,
which amounts to 1155.
I hope you're hungry.
You have no idea.
I apologize for the delay, sir.
Okay, I'll just...
What's the noise?
Uh-uh.
Audrey.
What are you doing?
What does that look like I'm doing?
We've been drinking.
What's all that?
So, if I made it anything...
What can't?
Why?
Because of who I am?
Because of who I am.
I feel so lost, so confused.
What was it?
Thank you, Frank.
For the time...
I'm trying...
...respect.
I think that's what I needed the most.
Frank.
makoo.
What else can we do?
What are we gonna do?
No, no.
Oh.
Jesus, we're not open yet.
It's an emergency.
I need to see the doctor immediately.
Right.
Dr. Coblin, if you'll come out here please we have an issue.
You'll have to fill out some papers dating the medical problem.
Actually?
My problem is not medical.
It's psychological.
Yes Laura.
What seems to be the problem?
Well for me.
Hating shots.
Number 1 is no gallon till you're getting shot.
So there's no senON getting old what's up with something that I don't have.
Give me the good news.
Doctor said I'm cured.
Frank, it hurts a lot.
I'll never let anyone hurt you a lot.
Mama's?
You know my fourth rule?
Never make a promise you can't keep.
Come on.
Close the door.
I can't keep.
Come on.
Close the door.
Eh.
Come on.
May I help you?
Check Billings to see Dr. Kaplan.
I'm sorry. He's out sick today.
I like Dr. Koblo.
Don't worry. Dr. Taibook's very nice.
Now if you'll just take him into room three.
Where's Miss Laura?
Who?
You're standing at her desk.
That Miss Laura.
She's out sick too.
There's a lot of flu going around.
Now come on.
Doctor's got a busy day.
Come on.
I'll be over before you know it.
Hey!
I'm Dr. Taibook.
Can't I wait for my doctor?
Unfortunately, your doctor was called away.
On emergency.
In that said he had the flu.
That was the emergency.
He came down with flu very quickly.
So, the sooner we start, the sooner we finish.
Eh?
Come. I show you something very cool.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Patient privacy in the room.
But you can wait in reception area or glass of water.
Okay. Trust me.
And Dr.
Please, it's a phone.
Yeah.
And I know.
Frank, I'm here.
You're early.
Yeah. We had fantastic telephones.
How far is my vacation?
Just like that.
From now on, it's the only way of flag-rank.
Telephones are nothing.
Where'd you made it?
Hello?
Sorry, Dr. Dunias is not in today.
Call back my thing.
I'm going to call.
Frank!
You know, maybe it's better if you wait for his regular doctor to come back.
It's very important that he receives immunizations.
I'm sure it is.
But a week won't make a difference.
No, we're doing...
No!
Get going, Jack!
I'm coming.
Look at me.
Remember my promise?
Yes.
I heard.
Remember my promise?
Yes.
It's me!
Get out!
Frank!
Shit.
The patient's not cooperating.
The car's the vehicle.
Come on, Harry.
Don't worry, everything's gonna be okay.
Frank!
Get down!
I'm not strong.
Take out a way.
Cut!
Plan B?
Yes, Plan B.
Oh, he made it.
Uh-huh.
What's that?
Jack's birthday present.
baseball uniform, cleats, glove, and a bat.
It's his favorite sport.
It was last year.
He's on a soccer team now and he's actually really good.
You know, you should see him sometime.
He's got a lot of things to do.
He's really good.
You know, you should see him sometime.
Hello?
Mr. and Mrs. Billings, they're coming!
Hi, everyone!
Yes.
Good morning, Mr. Driver.
Who is this?
You're looking at your review, Miro.
And you see him with his?
I know what you're thinking.
We'll approve class.
This is a rich judging from the little performance.
You put on back at the office because way beyond just driving children to school and back.
That's...
I'll approve class.
Stop at 7.62, I'm replacing round.
Wait.
Why'd you stop the car?
The border will be that way.
They're over 300 feet away.
Come on, Frank. Pick up.
None of this would have been necessary if you had no screw up my life.
So, now I'm going to tell you how to set things right.
Someone is going to appear in a few seconds.
I'm going to get you.
Let her in.
Driver.
Good boy.
Hi.
Leave it on.
Personally, I hate kids.
I don't know what your feelings are on the subject,
but if you ever want to have any, make no moves,
but the move I tell you to make.
You're in her hands now, will you come here?
They can be very gentle hands.
They can be hands from hell. Trust me on this one.
Trust him on this one.
You're a drive.
Make a laugh.
I said laugh.
Listen, keep doing this.
You're awake.
But how many rides did we make?
They're going to catch us.
Let me do this by way.
So no one gets hurt.
Where's the front of that?
Let's save the front for later.
Listen, keep doing this.
You're awake.
But how many rides did we make?
They're going to catch us.
Let me do this by way.
So no one gets hurt.
Where's the front of that?
Let's save the front for later.
We do this by way.
So no one gets hurt.
Where's the front of that?
Let's save the front for later.
I'm going to get the front of that.
Let's go south.
Not bad.
Did your mother ever teach you to say thank you?
Yeah.
She tried and failed miserably.
I think we lost them.
Think again.
Thought complete.
Let's go.
Who's the man?
You're worried.
What do you mean you can't find him?
He's one man in one car.
He's a chauffeur for Christ's sake.
Not exactly, sir.
I think there's a possibility you may have been in on it.
What's it possible?
How would you know?
He's been working here for a month.
He could have been setting this up the whole time
and you wouldn't own any different.
You are such an expert on knowing people.
His background.
He's special forces.
He didn't leave commando unit for five years,
specialized in search and destroy.
Been in and out of Lebanon, serious or down?
The man is out there.
I don't care what his skills are.
I don't care where he's from.
This is not a war zone.
This is an American city.
Where's my son?
That dance...
Something went wrong...
I lied to you...
Just let yourselves...
You're quite a guy.
Another time.
Another place.
You and me maybe.
The pleasure we get out.
Beauty.
Frank.
Frank!
Not what you expected when you reported for work this morning.
Is it, uh, Frank?
No.
Is that what passes with witness, sir?
This is my friend.
With?
It's not a requirement of the job.
Brutality.
Yes.
An ability to inflict pain, absolutely.
Certain psychotic moral ignorance, blind obedience, or repired.
So not with?
I was it.
Fine.
You didn't begin in my life.
What's this all about?
A timely question.
Max?
Pardon me.
Hello.
Put me on the speaker so you don't have to repeat instructions.
The next two hours you get $500 in consequential $100 bills,
you put them in a waterproof suitcase.
You go to the bayfront park personally.
There will be a blue Chrysler parked on the sand.
You place this suitcase in the trunk.
I do.
I don't know if I can get $5 million in two hours.
Mr. Billings, please, I read the newspapers.
The day you were appointed to your current position,
your network exceeded $100 million.
So?
You won't even feel the bite.
What?
Guaranteed or I have it.
You won't harm my son.
Guaranteed, Mr. Billings.
I'm not a car dealer.
Don't let the charming accent and my grammatically impeccable syntax mislead you.
You are leaving the jungle and in the jungle.
You either eat or be eaten.
But in the spirit of doing business here is the guarantee.
10 minutes past the deadline.
If the money doesn't arrive, I'll send a finger.
20 minutes.
Ah ha.
I thought.
Sounds like we have a deal.
Don't we miss the billings?
You have a deal.
Could we please speak to our son?
Mommy!
You have two hours, Mr. Billings.
Starting now.
You're my son.
Alright.
Frank, you promised you wouldn't marry me.
You promised!
Never make promises you can't keep my friend.
I don't.
It's one of my rules.
Wow.
Bravo.
A man who leaves his life by the rules.
But in my word, rules are meant to be broken.
Not mine.
This time we're going to have to make an exception.
Go.
Frank.
Take driver.
No, no, wait.
Wait. Wait.
A little distance between us isn't a bad thing.
Andiamo!
Now.
Hold on.
Ah!
Hello.
It's me.
We got them here, gentlemen.
You son of a bitch.
Look, I had nothing to do with this.
Watch scratch on his head.
One hair out of place.
Mr. Billings, let me speak to you.
It's in charge.
Hello, Frank.
This is you as much as David.
You have to act fast.
There are three boats.
Just tell us where you are.
Get a plane up over the interco-stalk.
Just tell me where you are, Frank.
Just tell us where you are.
Hello, Frank.
Got it.
Hello.
Tell Coney it's me.
Get out of the house.
I know.
We're just pretzins in Madeline.
Forget the Madelins.
Just get out.
And go where?
Anywhere.
The beach.
Go to the beach.
Oh, the beach.
I know.
Yeah.
You know, I know.
You know.
I know.
Oh, the beach.
Well, the famous Miami Beach.
Oh, my dream.
I would love to go to the beach.
Maybe not.
Hey!
How the fuck are you?
I'm the cook.
Oh, it's a mistake.
A terrible mistake.
Why we can't all just get on now.
Oh, no.
Hello?
It's Frank.
Don't hang up.
Pretend it's someone else.
Nice season.
Uh, no, I'm just here at home.
I didn't do it, Audrey.
She had a gun on Jacka.
I had no choice.
Yeah.
I saw that.
What do you know?
It's more than a kidnapping.
They called and asked for a ransom.
The doctors, they will think.
They were trying to give Jacka shot.
What are you interrupted them?
Audrey, I promise Jacka wouldn't let anyone hurt him.
I'm not going to bring that promise.
I'll call you back.
Audrey.
Is everything all right?
It's a pretty stupid question to ask right now.
Don't you think, Jeff?
All right.
So tell me again, Inspector Tarkone,
why you didn't immediately identify yourself as a police officer?
I was overwhelmed by the effectiveness of your preparation.
It's a sophistication, if you were a good one.
You know, I work in a small office in a small town.
We only have small crimes.
I must admit, I was a little insecure.
And you and Frank Martin are friends, right?
A friend.
I wouldn't say exactly a friend.
I know him.
We have a relationship.
A long relationship.
Hmm, not so long.
But they found you cooking at his house.
I'm French.
So?
We don't need to do someone for a long time in order to cook for them.
It's our way of breaking the ice.
Take, for example, this sandwich in coffee.
It's so grusty or friendly.
You will put on a metrosync, so bad it's not very good.
Yeah, no, it sucks.
What's that got to do with anything?
You have it too.
I'm going to put it on the table.
Don't move.
Smith.
Drop it.
Oh!
Are you sure this is safe?
Look over here, shoulder.
We got you covered.
As my mother used to say, a meal is only limited by your imagination.
It's Cambodian?
It's a cognizant.
Creme Brillet.
Cambodian?
Caught?
Caught mischir.
Where are you?
Cooking.
Can you talk?
Oh.
Speak out of this.
I'm going to put it on the table.
Mom!
Please.
Do you mind?
Thank you.
Vivaanmong.
Tramina Ivey.
I wish you a pleasant trip.
Vivaanmong.
I asked you a cooking for.
For the US marshals.
Once they found my badge, they were very polite.
They gave me a coffee in a sandwich.
They wouldn't believe what passes for food in this place, Frank.
But I'm correct in this situation.
What they read from a shift to call back and confirm everything.
Of course, that might take a while.
He's never there.
Anything about me?
Yes.
There are very interesting about you.
I want to know where you are.
Where are you?
No, if I'm very long.
Listen, hold on.
Do you have access to a computer?
Is yours in having access to something decent to it?
Oh.
And some fellow.
Who is it?
It's what I need to know.
Do they have an IT program?
You'll forgive me, bit.
I'm not so used to this system.
Back home there is one computer for ten of us.
So, I'm not sure if you're right.
I've been doing this for a long time.
I'm not sure if you're right.
I'm not sure.
It's the same.
Not sure if you're right.
I'm not sure.
So, I'll leave you to the system.
Back home there is one computer for ten of us.
So, how is it with you, Frank?
I said complicated story.
Are you being around this shit?
I'd say that.
In other words, you're not of a state.
Ah.
Well, Russian biologist.
We've had to run this.
Degrees from the state laboratory for biological warfare and cyber.
But----
I'm not going to let you down.
No!
Get out!
What is happening?
You want to catch your bus?
No!
Come on!
What are you doing, driver?
That's so cool, that's what I was, I know!
No!
Tell me about the doctor's office.
The one where you try to stick the kid with this.
Want to tell me?
No!
She knows you're a driver.
Do you know what's left of it?
Obviously something no conducive to your good health.
She's all I needed to know in the first place.
Have a good life.
What's left of it?
No!
I would post a base, the ransom is still there.
Nice.
The ransom still hasn't been picked up.
What does that mean?
Don't worry, right now it means nothing.
What if it's not just a kidnapping?
I think that if they don't take the ransom, I'm going to get my son back.
Audrey, don't make this any more complicated than it already is.
I'm not making this complicated, Jefferson.
It's because of your job.
What is my job back to do with any of this?
It has everything to do with it.
Do you understand?
Because you became famous, we became the targets.
No matter what any of you all think, the only one who's out there trying to get Jack back is Frank.
Frank?
The chauffeur?
You spoke to Frank Martin.
The last person who shot Jack alive!
We found the boy.
Get shut down.
Hard drive, Blue.
We're giving him a win in there.
Yes, sir.
How long is it going to take?
The boy is faster than we can.
He can suffocate in there.
Stay calm.
It's my son.
Audrey, let them work.
Are you just going to sit there and do nothing?
Audrey!
They're experts.
Everyone is an expert.
I'm happy with all of you.
Let's go.
You okay?
Are you going to the boy?
Breathe.
Come on, breathe.
You're the devil.
I wish.
Breathe.
To me, three.
You're stupid, didn't you?
Where is some of it? He's in chamber.
I need to speak with him. He won't be long.
I need to speak with him.
He's in Panasonic.
He's rapping.
I'm going to the boy.
Come on, rascal!
Come on!
You're going to be a dead man.
What was that?
I don't know.
What are you doing here?
I need anecdote.
The driver.
He inject me with virus.
Walk!
Do you meet with where would he get the virus?
The one with less.
I need to find out where he is.
Where would he get the virus?
The one who left in Dr. Sudjery.
Please.
I ain't at the point.
I'm sick.
Come down.
You're not sick.
You have four hours before the virus is active.
You know that.
You weren't on creatin' it.
Open fridge.
I'm telling you.
Ah!
Is the need here?
Open fridge.
Over the fridge.
This insurance policy, how many will have two doses?
Enough for Tifa than myself.
Oh, no!
People supposed he canceled.
There is one for me.
And I want it now.
Come on.
Let's do it.
That's not.
What are you?
Right.
There is enough for two of us.
You don't need it.
Do you injected me?
With water.
I'm not sick.
Not sick.
What?
Water.
Sort of bitch.
Good.
A problem is solved.
One does for each of us.
Not for us.
One for you.
One for the child.
You're the version.
It's touching.
My patience is about to run out.
No.
Ah!
Hey!
Tell me about the virus.
OK.
What you must know.
Everything.
The start is what is it?
It's a recombinant retroimmune double polymorphine
that you have going to the child will die.
Anyone who breathes on with die, then it's over.
You mean it, Soma?
You know this is designed to go in there after 24 hours.
Thanks for the lesson.
Now give me the files.
You really want to play superhero, don't you?
Well, let's see if you can fly.
Ah!
Hey!
You OK?
OK.
There's nothing to worry about.
It's just a simple viral infection combined
with the stress of what happened.
It should pass in a day or two.
I gave him something to help him sleep.
Call me if anything arises.
Thank you.
Thank you, Doctor.
No.
Audrey.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
I'm going to be late.
Audrey, all this is...
Well, it's made me realize what a fool I've been.
Jack.
And with you.
Are you okay?
Mr. Bill, we're running late.
We'll be right out.
I'd like to come by after the conference.
Check on Jack.
Check on you.
Good.
I'll see you soon.
They're here if you need them.
Are you all right, ma'am?
I'm fine.
Hello?
It's me.
You're okay, Mrs. Bill.
I got to see you a bit, Dr.
Hi, Susan.
How are you?
I'm alone.
Great, Frank.
I'm done with.
Frank, you were wrong.
It was a kid napping.
Jack is fine.
Jack's been infected with a deadly virus, Audrey.
Now anyone who comes into contact with him will die.
What are you telling me?
Are you telling me that my son is going to die?
No, he's not.
I'm not going to die.
I want to think you better the virus becomes airborne.
So when you want to breathe down, it gets infected.
Some was a weapon.
The target is this far.
Jefferson?
Oh, why?
Because of the conference.
It's the only logical answer.
Drug enforcement agency in the hemisphere in one room.
Now, it's been breathed the room dies.
Oh, please.
You better trust me, Audrey.
I'm sorry.
Can you get to him?
What are you going to do?
I'm going to go responsible.
There's more of this.
For you and everybody else.
For you now.
We have a guest.
He burning up.
Okay.
You got to go.
Go.
Don't move!
Oh!
Is the governor here?
Every fight is going to be here.
The governor delegates from all over the world.
What's he saying?
Hello?
You can't go to the conference.
Everything all right?
To give him a deadly vibe.
Audrey, I can't hear you.
I'm inside.
Now I've got it.
I'll see you back.
You all right?
All right.
Come on.
Let's get ready.
I know.
You still a guest of the government?
No. You gave me the first accommodation.
Let me guess.
You knew the computer.
It's practically my pillow.
So?
I don't know. I have nothing.
My favorite type of investigation.
Let's see.
Hello.
I'd like to take this opportunity to introduce you to my delegates.
Please.
That's right.
Breathe, my friend.
Breathe.
Tomorrow, this bus starts around the way
and that corporation agreements are dead in buried.
You know what your biggest problem is going to be?
What?
Counting the money.
Can't wait for tomorrow.
Ah!
It's easy, isn't it?
Johnny Chelindee.
The highest in South-Houth,
21 looking to the trouble.
But the repurgates are something that...
Someone accessed the database on the 15th floor.
That's Gonzalez.
He's on vacation.
Ah!
He was behind the host-stakes of the public ministers in Geneva.
It was a nice piece of work.
Give me an address.
Miami is Thailand.
But it can drive number 26.
We found the car.
One great cup, so call it.
Thank you for the compliment.
Maybe not.
Oh my God, man!
Oh!
Stop!
Send this guy to my car, you're right.
I'm coming.
Miami.
I think I'm better.
A little bit.
Should I try to go back to sleep?
Okay.
Man, are you all right?
Thanks.
Thanks, help me!
Oh!
Thanks!
Help me!
Oh!
Thanks!
Okay, do it.
What are you doing?
You know last night got me thinking.
How do you transport the antidote safely?
We need something that won't break.
Something that can't be stolen.
Something totally secure.
But it's good to have a good time.
If we don't have a good time, we'd be late.
But we'll be late.
We'll be late.
Okay, let's go.
I can't be stolen. Something totally secure.
Me?
Impressive.
Get dressed.
Stop it.
Is this your friends?
Not yet.
Where'd they go?
The garage.
I'm out of ammo.
Me too.
So am I. Where are the reloads?
The garage.
Check now! Go, go, go!
Ah!
What do you want me to do?
Keep the made of running.
What?
Don't worry baby.
It's safe now. It's safe.
You're so beautiful.
Remind me of my yellow poop rider.
Ah!
Don't move.
Oh, Mr. Driver.
Where are you in tomorrow?
But then I believe what you came for all over the floor
he wouldn't want this for you.
Not after you walked so hard try to get to the antidote.
Take a good look, Freddie Martin.
I'm a cure for what aids you.
I'm the only cure for what aids you.
I am the antidote.
When I was dry I'm impressed.
Didn't give you enough credit to come to the driver
to figure this out.
I'm figured it all out yet.
Perhaps I can help you. What part are you leaving with how you say it?
Think of you.
Why?
Oh, that's the easy part.
It's a business that you're pure and simple.
I'm for hire to the highest bidder.
And in this case the highest bidder was the Colombian cocaine cartels
that wanted this pesky lumen afterbacks.
You really think killing all these politicians
is going to make things easier for them?
That's not my problem.
I'm sorry to do a job.
I did the job.
Like you just did.
My pay is better.
My hair and my suit too.
Oh, Lola.
Now if you'll excuse me, I have a plan to catch you.
Okay, name it.
Charge out.
Don't have Blake.
Pleasure.
You're killing me.
Hey!
I'm going to kill you.
We're coming to you right from the Keyviscan Car's way.
At least 10 for these cars.
I'm in heart for sheet of the stolen red picket truck.
Aright, this is just not.
It's just not Jim, are you getting that?
There's another car that is swaying past the police
as if there was standing still.
Looks like...
So Mitch can drive.
How much on this one?
Yes, he can.
BraWhite
If clearance for take up Mr. Chilini, sit back and enjoy your flight and we will be in Columbia before you know it.
I'm going to be in the air.
There will be a problem with the landing gear.
We won't come back to land.
We fly with a problem.
Theoretically, then you land where we get to Columbia.
Once if you can lift the menu.
Sorry for the inconvenience, Mr. Chilini. I don't know where you're going.
Sorry. Flight's been cancelled.
I'm sorry to inform you that you have been cancelled.
Never see it.
Relax.
It's a dream.
Let's get to know each other.
I think I know everything I need to know.
I'm sorry.
Five points.
What has eyes but no ears, skin but no hair.
It's white inside and brown outside.
Mom?
Wrong.
Dad?
The catapult.
Wrong.
A potato.
May I help you?
I was just leaving.
You'll be out of here.
Wrong.
Snake.
A peanut.
Yeah.
A hot dog.
Wrong.
That was best.
Yeah.
Didn't want you to miss your plane.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Five points.
Check it off the bus.
You will believe I have to meet us like that.
I have something for you.
You figure since you never got to the beach.
I know water, water, sandy sand, ears, it's all the same.
I have one like two or six nights in Paris.
Thank you Frank.
It was an interesting vacation.
What more could one ask for?
Yeah.
A laugh on it.
A laugh on my friend.
Have a good flight.
I doubt it.
So I said it's all that wins.
I guess we can have everything we wish for it, can we?
No, we can't.
Yeah.
I'm looking for a transporter.
I'm listening.
My tastes have been empresa.
My company has been Oreo tango.
I'm listening.
This is me talking to you some reason.
Hey!
Hey.
You're sitting here.
Calm down.
Chill!
Shit!
Relax!
Yun sellos!
Stay calm, Fu.
I don't want to stay, I'm super far not, man, I don't want to break
So give it up baby, you're not in control
Don't let the sun rise till your soul
You say no, I'm not a mess, it's really un-bestaid
I'm super far not, let it ain't gonna break
Just let it on and rock, let it win and rock
Don't let the sun rise till your soul
You say no, I'm not a mess, it's really un-bestaid
Don't let it still your soul
I want something, I want something more
Don't let the sun rise till your soul
You say no, I'm not a mess, it's really un-bestaid
I want something, I want something more
Don't let the sun rise till your soul
You say no, I'm not a mess, it's really un-bestaid
I'm the ground, something made me fall
I'm the second, the dark, the light down
Someone made me fall in the city of San Luis
Don't let the sun rise till your soul
You say no, I'm not a mess, it's really un-bestaid
I want something more, I'm not a mess, it's really un-bestaid